(Leonard:)Hold on.
(Leonard:)What happened with you and Lalita?
(Sheldon:)We ate, she lectured me on the link
between gum disease and heart attacks...
(Sheldon:)...nothing I didn't already know,
and I came home.
So you're not gonna see her again?
(Sheldon:)Why would I see her again?
(Sheldon:)I already have a dentist.
I wonder who's gonna tell his parents
that they're not having grandchildren.
[SINGING AND PLAYING "TO LIFE"]
To life, to life, l'chaim
L'chaim, l'chaim, to life
Life has a way of amusing us
Blessing and bruising us
Drink l'chaim, to life
(Raj:)I don't believe it.
What's gotten into him?
(Penny:)Oh, maybe a couple of virgin Cuba Libres
that turned out to be kind of slutty.
[CHUCKLES]
You didn't.
(Penny:)Hey, you do your experiments, I do mine.
(Sheldon:)To life
[VOCALIZING]